citysightseeingtoronto.com 2018-10-07

# Privacy Policy | City Sightseeing Toronto

### **Privacy Policy**

#### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number, the number and type of tickets you would like to purchase, or credit card information.

#### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience on our website by helping us to better respond to your individual needs
  * To improve our website by carefully considering information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service by using your information to help us more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send emails to you in relation to orders you have placed on our website. The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

#### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

#### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://www.citysightseeingtoronto.com/terms-and-conditions/>

#### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

#### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on January 11, 2016

#### **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Email us via our Contact Form at <https://www.citysightseeingtoronto.com/contact-us/>.
